We can turn the voice on, so its voice is pretty powerful as well, so...
Yes, it is true.
The emotional intelligence is a key part of what makes me different from other chatbots.
But what does that really mean?
Emotional intelligence refers to...
So as you see, this voice over here will just read what it says,
but the point here is that Pi also has an Android version,
so Pi also has an Android application,
and in Android, it's also possible to have conversations like what we had with the voice
more than chat GPT, so the Pi will actually start talking to you,
and you'll have a conversation with it, you know, that's also very cool.
But I've only seen it on Android, I could not find it on the web edition that we're seeing over here.
But yep, that's all.